know the names. Many of us were abused by them. Now together as survivors, we will
confidentially compile the names. We all know we're regularly in the Epstein world
and it will be done by survivors and for survivors. We are the keys to this situation. We have
the truth and the FBI knows the truth. The government knows the truth. You may pull the
wool over the sheep's eyes, but we are the keys. We know who was involved.
Hoppers must choose. Will you continue to protect predators or will you finally protect survivors?
In the year 2000, I was taken to Jeffrey Epstein's island while on a photo shoot in the Caribbean.
Epstein's reach went to the very top of fashion. Everyone in the industry knew, yet he was too
powerful to stop. But I ask you why. Who was he to our government that he was allowed to operate
openly for decades? We know the game. We know the players. And we are sitting here for 20 years
waiting for you to get up and do something. Well, guess what? Your time is up and now we're doing it.
What we heard today is a coverup. And it is a coverup of epic proportions. A coverup involving the United
States government, the justice system, rich and powerful individuals. A coverup potentially
involving foreign countries and foreign actors. And yes, here today in this house, as our colleagues
are up in the House chamber in the rules committee, a coverup by the Republicans in this chamber.
We will hold you all accountable for this miscarriage of justice, for the abuse of these women and
the abuse of this institution to try to cover it up. Because there happens to be a very powerful
person at the top who doesn't want these stories out. So that is why we subpoenaed these records.
That is why these victims were here today to bravely tell their stories. And whatever
justice looks like in the coming days and weeks and years, we will follow every thread. We will
follow every piece of evidence. We will follow every bank record. We will follow every investigation.
We will follow every court order. And we will make sure that those who were abused by these men
are held accountable.